Early early.
Early.
Early. Early.
Warning.
Wrong
were all
mad
.
Men
Were
right man coming up on
a pack dynamite it says underneath. That's
a minute I'll put it if you got my last
name but I am let's get. That one exactly
against automatic life I went down and read
it first got into it and snapped out of
our I don't know what it was paper it
was a chain of command wanted. To say
a few words with
a puppy I don't know what to say that
thing still has all come out so I have to
listen Mom I won mom and
there isn't a mark on a not
a mark I'll be home to sweetheart
but don't wait up for me that's.
I know you do the same thing if you had
a mother like mine but anyway I want to
thank you. For the championship anyway
I guess back in the good ole USA where.
You remember this.
Mother's Day.
Is too busy trying to keep the step
from escaping the back and that right.
Sure that's.
The first thing one notices
about a man. You know
a lot of people. Say.
Is that how you identify. Yes. You
better get along back to the mark as does
my start trouble if you label loans along
. OK.
Finding out it was.
Because the. Rest of.
The world.
So either the president got to go no no no
no he's gone for the day go I go I want
to go well you got
a drink well give me some more I
want to. Change it we won the
championship then we were right up there
on the money you're going to have
a lot of things. That
something's going to get
a sense of. Right now it's like
older activists like they.
Have enough Now come on they also.
Said to me. That they think
that the golden time of all I
do want to do that will
be that we may be just.
The icing. On the Media. To
stop what not this is but
I just don't like the.
Way they have their legacy of the
elite in the get the job I think.
I can say I get. The job
I get they get the same.
Thing when you want to play the.
Yankees. You want to find maybe Johnny.
Had left the line I don't think the
put you why do you realize that
this being said why don't.
You know cut it up.
To get part time.
Why don't you go. Daddy don't be like that
but you. I don't like it much I don't
like that kind of kidding it's like this
you can talk that way to my friend's
friend nobody's got any friends. You
may not agree. But he's got brand
friends yeah my friends
a fifty percent to my friends right
my friend. Take my ROM I watch him
get away with it he wouldn't talk like that
I go I just stay. In the fight records
I mean nobody does anything unless it's
a minute if you do it except
your mother. The last.
I've got
a. Good line is that
shut it.
Down he said. He would get up not to get.
Your. Record.
Right the morning traffic you would think
was going just read your paper which is
always nice when you think of a
better story well so long just
a minute. Oh yes. We have.
An echo so every time I
see you. Leaving Yes.
He's all right.
Lol. But. Nothing he did.
To do that thought Kerik coming to work on
a slope which handgun is are
probably going to get around.
On helping get him out of here where we
going have to makea nobody there. Get those
folks. In their purse.
Go ahead I mean the guy
maggots talking about me.
Come tell us No it doesn't
work well going to my house.
And I have
a shot thanks ladies well
at my door when me. We
get
a scram out of your quick no I'm going to
stick I got it all right you stick solar
thank you get stuck Are you sure he did
it I'm telling you he's fuckin with that
let the Is and when he doesn't go down the
youth about to repeat blow up over the
head of the whiskey bottle and the guy
goes down unconscious himself up for kicks
on the whiskey that Osama Johnny tell me
to cure when he's broke they don't tell
him what that they will do when she wakes
up will all be that you want me to always
eventually think yeah well we were there
when we get think he's going to say we
didn't do anything to get think he's gonna
take the rap while we walk out but we
did the thing shut up you said that once
and explained to you you know I think if
you do anything is can you prove it can you
prove you didn't do nothin. The Johnny
would sing then you know he'd go to the
chair boy wouldn't you just heard him say
you know sucker. If we can stick
together you would be kidding.
He said you take his role and his wife and
his gal I'm no shocker either someone.
Has to get this scared of me because I
want to like it and we head out to cover
this whole thing before.
It's. A
very big. But I think number two way
twelve forty three Look for Johnny brought
them all the way traveling
with manager doc what
a girl Goldie what reporter killed at
a park. There after Don't let him get it
sucks all right maybe I won't I won't pick
up Ray convertible for license
number two way twelve forty three.
There are
a few. I
am.
Then facts. Like the fact
that the fact. That fact
the fact that we all find X.
Factor.
In do
what.
Lose. A little.
And hit it went on.
The Lead. Are Not sure what that I
said What are you talking
that way for chillis man like
a riding cello lessons what you're doing
here then I want to ask you want to know
is about saying I'm
a wrist watch Yeah I know I can read I
read about in the papers to. Still I watch
my girl Mike. Serves him right I'm sorry
about girlie she was OK she wouldn't die
because that was him recently you know
that you're guilty of the murder of this
newspaper man let it talk in that way
for I start to hit him and then I don't
remember your started to hit
him and he's dead and he
a newspaper man you're as good
as dead what do you talk in
a way for your as good as dead what are
your efforts for your dead you're the guy
that burned up in the car you came to me
for advice this is my advice stay dead let
Johnny bread because state that you be
somebody else be Jack object on me now get
out of New York. I need to money
I've got ten grand in the National
Trust back you can't go to the
bank don't you want to stand in
a bottle I have to help my pocket you write
on me nobody of he made nobody want let
me have a copy I'll get it for you when
you do that sure there go to this address
a there and you hear from me he bought
a sight I haven't any money I'm going
to send. A ten dollars when I will do
a ten dollars What do you think you're not
going to nightclubs OK and well I have
you know Mark yes tomorrow this is the
address yeah now don't be seen by anybody I
guess if you're saying you'll be tried for
murder so talk that way when you grow
a beard or something to change your appearance
OK I'll do something I didn't figure
that.
And we find the death of John Bradfield
in Golden West accidental causes while
abating arrest for the murder of Charles.
Well the papers can't walk this time. And
six hours later we not only discover who
committed the crime but we also know that
he's dead and you imagine the whole of
this hadn't happened killing reporters one
thing the papers won't stand for. That
human factor sure gotta kill one of the
game either. I think exactly I don't think
that either burned up or don't even feel
it's all right in that remember me putting
that watch on his right hand when the
guy they brought in had that much on all
right but it was only slept so what can
a guy changes watchman's right wrist was
left of the lever might well something the
guy always does the same way like the
side he starts to shave on in the morning
Chris so I think with the wrist watch
failing you've been hanging around step so
much you're saying things that's
what saying things. I did
another thing that once was in the third
when I started on Johnny battles wrist I
put it in the first told you heard him tell
me do it himself so one wrist is bigger
than the other in jeopardy or that maybe
all I ask is that you're reopen the case
and assign me reopen the case now get
this violent Johnny Bradfield and it was
Johnny Bragg Bill who banged up on
the highway this morning at five am
a little listen to hope the trouble with
you failing is that ever since your
railroad or the wrong guy that I think.
You're screwing Why don't you retire.
Tell you why because I'm not oh yes you
are but you don't know what I'll show you
if I'm. To that guy they brought in isn't
Johnny bread you will let me try to
phrase. You for ten years you've been
picking on me just because I made
a mistake well maybe this is your mistake
maybe if I prove it I'll put you on more
detail like you did me I'd love to
secure it. All right you got yourself an
assignment thank you expect.
Today I want to get my
money as I got your money.
Hundred one hundred fifty two hundred two.
Dollars and I mean that's mine now but I
will. Put as much distance between myself
and this city as my money with my ten
grand to fifty enjoy the rest of it is my
feet what do you mean where is the rest
of my ten grand I've explained it to you
is my See what are you trying to do make.
Money you think you would hand over the
rest of that ten grand. Now listen to me
and I'll give you some advice don't. Take
that chance of yours with the right stuff
way back someone's going to spite you
what you don't seem to understand Donnie
jackdaw me remember that Jack dawning
think you don't remember that.
What I started to say Donny. Don't take
that stance of yours don't you just.
Not at all you'll be killing some other man
or if you don't give yourself away help
away once they get through your life isn't
worth doing only stay away from places
stay away from places. Afraid from
now you have got to be afraid.
I guess that's my advice
in the grand. Saga.
What can I do with this two hundred
fifty dollars I want to see
a long way and what do you want more for
you don't want to usually train with that
people are going to want to
use an automobile you'll have
a preacher what one question
a thing and keep the money for food
that ought to last at least six months.
Of the of.
The the the
the Mako
the New
Orleans.
Yes without my money that's why you're wrong
buddy that's my money not your money.
It went up there I got
a new belt I just got out. I'm
out of you. And take
a walk. Where.
Shall.
We live.
I faxed it back you made. Love not
a tramp. I
could go. Well yes it's
a nice one much to pick with I'll be swell
to notice that he's like around the moon
but you'd think. It might be I
carry a hook accompanied by
a white flag but nice day
here hold your card.
Whether there's a chance but
it is a big chance it's
a matter of fact Aronsen back at Indy
and ask you pick me back or you get
a handout I'm no tramp. I know your big oil
man and you came all the way down here
to study about
a line I suppose you have an easy pocket
Bo's I told you I did have an amazing COAS
. I no longer beauty but if you want
a kick out of kick. I going
to hunch I wouldn't have
a mill here anyway. Right with me you
know the Waldorf right around the corner
gotta try to carry a bank I'm
a sucker for Java. In.
The old is poor.
Old the break up they
were pretty. Nigh like best. Of all.
If it was a magnet she faded
but come on give humanity
a we don't want to knock out the facts in
the middle come out that like we're not.
Good but.
You're Golden that you're
golden. It is gold where
we're stuck in it. I want to know. Where
you're at Rancho repartee about twenty
miles from killing Arizona and.
I get it. And what's the take and the
kind of long count I save in Africa today
where was I hit my stomach
I think of eating for
a week. Or less that milk
you're here because. It
shows they like umbrella that I'm. Being.
Nice and quiet around here.
Nobody much rather know just
me and Grandma here. What do you do with
yourself or the ranch I don't get it you're
not the kind. You know that like the
ranch's daughter the name Look
suppose you tell me about your.
New. Place and you do that again
and you'll be up early quite to
a few months I wouldn't call that
he can arrest me for trying.
Right here we are. Sure of how they
did call our kicking ass girl oh
so there's
a they are about passed out on our shed
disavowing our right Ray from born at Texas
I've been cut. Throat and face that is
poked around here no no no I'm I took
a bag of Texas I've been just because
we're still thinks pick up down there. On
a the high alone shit the
feet are not to be had
a chill day Sure sure it's all right I'll
be on the way now just wanna stop. And
she about the kids forgot to make my report
the board you know that they care about
a chap on calming effect on me and I think
sure why not OK out he was like that's
a like
a lot when you know better Yeah I'd like
to get out of here to the big and walk.
Outside.
It is. A little.
Old
a little the old.
Way where you're going to live.
What you do just want to
walk into
a job drink you would see that Grandma
cracking down on truth. Like you
think but in the typical crap it's OK to
kill or you really get hurt because trying
to get the victim if you can forgive apply
have to cite football picks I back to
savage it all I just touched I'm gonna go
take a walk without some kid firing off
a twenty one gun salute or Sir
you were the only without being
a watchman even for you don't want me to
hang around here forever do you I told you
I was looking for work by the trunk you
might to the nearest town don't want to let
him go the sheriff has
a place to hold those I turned on looking
for work so I can do nothing to remember
that you talk like I was
a criminal to hear the tell me what you're
looking for you know this country that
hang around here I get it it kept me
a couple of days now you want me to work
it all for what I want to be accurate
a great big lazy lemon of
a face like your excellent and you know
around here for what he wanted to go I
heard you got
a car into that fight you know like you can
sit around in the sun and I mean I was
a kid. It's
a music chariots. I'm
.
We're not
a new. York New York thank you I've
been there boy do I miss that age group
yeah not reform school was going to I guess
you missed that. Reform School and so I
mean burns been up there twice you don't
get out twenty one yeah he got a lease on
a joy. Just
what is the set up oh we got too hot in New
York City set aside here to reform Yeah
well the ravening jever hear of him but
he was never my church minded Well anyhow
he was a priest. So he died about
a year ago he got up that help by
neighbor from the center of gets out to
a system that's the only one for to get
the generator made generated your dog
regenerated I mean three Born
Free from school for kids.
Yeah but they ain't going to regenerate
me cuz I'm going back to how you go by
Pullman going to take a special
airplane I'm going to through
a bank you're going to through
a back like him you ain't got to know if
you ain't got the no I. Was the thing out
of Tommy sister yeah what you know she
didn't know she supposed to watch Tommy get
the generator regenerate
a lot. Yet it would have been time to
reform school if I was like capital I don't
think it's the generated. That. I want
to try to market me no only could to try
to write. You know Sam is a pretty
tough guy they got him Robin
a way out they got me for advice and guidance
every three to back in car wreck get
a match what you got there but
a quanta but you want what do you kids would
know where I get some real butts would
you get a sellable Reza
stand there or to use
a small can grow as when you're going to
help yourself that they wouldn't be on the
around here though stealing my homework I
thought you said it was tough for them
and it's not about you
but it's a great move in
a fight another one of them my
line that still made my mom wait
a minute I dare you to get me
so what did they gotta take
a day off I ain't going to
take it they tell me it's
a good day and. I
can have
a drink yeah yeah I'll get one for. P.R.
The.
Boy just hit the spot.
To get him to here he
a nice work now very nice work getting kids
to steal for you there's anything lower
than that I haven't married yet.
They. Waited. As long as the referee.
Going to. Your right and
you move in like that when you
turn your head around you take
a left hook and you. Said I
If the referee sees it the
trick is to get the other guy between you
and the referee says. I don't know I
think about it.
What are you doing so I. Don't
get to do that again today.
OK it's.
All right. I love it can't
get the stamina think
given the family are like this. I get it
only hotter and quicker but make sure
you've got the other guy between you and
referee OK to be defeated because he would
take you always but me I want to leave
us men alone can get my head I was just
teaching
a kid out to take him so yeah with dirty
tricks and somebody I'll pull him out of
my mind as well learn to put him first you
don't leave anything on the level do you
do you I know you are not what about you
well what about me playing probation
officer and you saw what Getting go for no
gimme that I know all about that priest
in New York he did yeah what about the fun
there isn't any fun to stop when he died
trying to tell me you and your lady is
supporting these kids on the cover to write
what. You wouldn't understand. You must
have some angle I wonder if you are as
tough as you think you are. Tough but I am
a sucker reader what do you call it from
well your stuck up what you tell me is
true so is that old lady thought that
that priest was because you put out
a helping hand help yourself as my
slogan and want to get you. A lot of.
Thanks for the listen. Sixty.
Five hundred gallons buy
a full tank. One thousand nine hundred
thirty eight dollars and still.
Time is spent doing in the service space
Yeah well some of the stuff Tommy joins
the Big Brother movement I want to get
a bike to look at if you don't just
a baby she was doing all I want to anybody
about the ring only selling enough to
pay for food not even behind in taxes and
this is money that's coming from New York
. The place before. Them I
talk about yeah I heard
until. A rancher got back to New York
who are not a big softy and then
a gas station are zero point two miles one
way and twenty eight the other. They pay
at the place during weekdays Plus many
On Sunday I think what the Meadowlands.
Looks like he's
a generated All right. I just know that he
was going to call all the programs what
do you expect to use for money do you think
you'll stick up when he gets big enough
. To have three. Talking about.
It to you several the way. That some kids
get this one down the road several miles
but knew that went with a really
good we're watching for want of
a gun about the time see anybody that's
where we once went to get what's understood
I. Never thought I wanted
to hear what you want to.
Wallow. For. Here I can.
I also want to Jack Kerouac's now oh
OK you're the fixated on the now.
Great writer. Who. Write
about it. And what you are
scared up trying to. Write
a filmmaker and you know how to
swim or no matter I must tell you.
And now it's not
a lot of water and. I mean this is the
drama and the you are great and great you
don't hear me. OK OK you are right.
And you're amazing. OK to be
a pretty good kid came back you go to. I
want to go but I think that they are filled
up much of it with it I want to. Live
out the last year. And sacrifice
money out of him over the.
Public mess if you will
a lot of it would have required that you
laid out any particular gravel he would i
can't thank.
You do you think.
Are you sure you're telling
me the truth might hurt on
a thank you I don't know what he went well
did they say where they were going just
took the truck and left how long ago.
It's down to ten feet and still for all
we have to stick together when we want to
go down we catch one again I'm tired.
Make. Sure I am right what do we do not.
Wait till.
Three. Am I want to go down
to see what's up on the spank
we have on for
a few minutes Gallo to. Think. About
that and what's more I have to go to people
don't get down it's time to kick the
can and I thought.
I could live on
a limb so I can think I think it's gone
down there oh yeah I'm going to take time
to get sick.
And. I put on. One more
time going to look good.
They've been looking all over the
place I know this guy has always done
a road kill. Grama they couldn't have taken
the truck to town I'll let don't want
to pin you down there all right
quite right. It was all right.
Commented you.
Reach for that matter and
break it down OK guys.
I'm. All right.
This guy sounds more like a five it's a
space on the spot thing up not doing
a good job you think you found it maybe
you'll be all right. Nobody talked he got
away to let me follow him
a lot and we fished about it that. We hadn't
seen him since about two o'clock this
afternoon I left in the truck I don't know
if you know if I don't know whether he
wins when you say. Oh.
Never mind scared me but.
Where have you been we took the truck and
one way down to know what I was going to
get no read your stuff to watch him and
again before we knew what was getting soft
was an angel.
I know went to the
spring. College could be
a red robe and so well well
what did you do to. Fall on
a narrow gauge and ditch. Tonight it's all
fall in the same irrigation ditch we got
wet fishing them out and they got
telephones you know now where we was
so I don't expect to get the truth out of
you or any of them while you around. In
fact I think we have enough general So OK
when May when he want to go the sooner
the better I'll leave right now that's how
you feel about it Peggy you don't know
what got up. I
gotta tell you today I feel OK then we
was quite like cats and I trust you mean
right I mean you know Jack just like
want to dump a bunch of kids a van in
a bucket of water that's right there we
want to thank. Our cut out whatever time it
got to make me like this all over think
that's good for me when Anyway you know
want to think that we'd all
be dumped it wasn't a Jack-O.
Because certainly. Why don't
you like tell me she'd say was
my fault for taking your hands out to take
anybody with you have you when you mean
YOU LOTS of
a child come around in pairs like that what
about that gas station I actually live
in and if don't come back. I'd like to thank
you kids but this is that has been an
issue about after me for kidnapping. I only
not sure how many and I appreciate it.
But then again. And you cause enough trouble
for one day I'd like to talk to Jack
alone OK just begun.
But on your mind. John
a skeptic Well it's. A joke only the truth
about what happened I said I was sorry I
did not want to hear but I can assure you
that the build up another side of the
nose no into your. Head that guy
I put it up it was not really
grandma but I did later now. You are
going to have to leave I sure want to.
You know. There's only one reason
I want to stay you. Your mistake.
Cracked at that. I got
a girl can have everything which is like
the drive to town I got married. Today
pretty good use of some
supper not. A thing in.
Mind let me say I know
a spot on the side of the road where no
cause of the supposedly putting. In what
form I'm. Crazy about is
a bad enough. Yes Mark this is
not wrong way how the wrong way.
I'm leaning
a batch to who you are actually if you name
it it isn't James you sound like I was
proposing marriage when
I was. Not my dad. Oh.
Your frank way want to be frank
do. You want me to prove I'm.
Going on closing let me thank you kindly
for the write home. The wrong hands.
Try to make love you know if you're trying
to get away with murder. You know action
the big city to an awful lot of lines.
So it's up to made a think of a new line
a movie when you. Think oh.
I'll be with. I did I think if you get
in and I'm going on with our great
what if you listen even once
a bit back to that bright color up yeah
with the change I wanted to get some good
at this time so you can try out my new
palm at that address put together in the
still operation bubbly explode OK I got
this one little Larry if you can use I just
came in and asked how much
thirty cent. Very said too much
just.
Going to take and I hear is good and if
you're any good it will be Boston bombing
suspect only much he put it what are
they going to go by when I don't know if
anybody can pick what we just took
a lot of money. I guess that is. Not
enough of Happily though. And I wouldn't
get my ring with that big ugly most of
five thousand dollars around
while all of Europe would find
a killer to me. Was that it actually took
a gallon of dollar twenty eight charges
for exactly that bill going kind of high
How about
a lot of ways you get some time. I guess I
can do my bit for paying in the ole the
things that are for me nice
pop. He's a pretty good on
a touch of speed I can't complain that's
one thing they can say well they got to
have gas they got to have what this pump
set you back about two grand just about
and say what
a big improvement that is over the whole
hand. I'm going to cause grief for
a few minutes of picking comes to be right
back oh I. Turn but what's that got
to do with it if I want to I'm
not worried about you it's
a customer I don't pay daughter she said
I'll give that guy plenty of fight I'm
having a fight. I got
a lot of work to do and I want to
check that mug grandma. Oh you.
Come out of I get I don't.
You know. You'll be
a pleasure. When you my.
Darling calm. About anything your
troubles are over we're going to open
a gas station. And I think that. The
statistics you know they wouldn't get they
should I want forty two miles one way and
twenty eight the other. Any idea what
a gas station cars I've been to that you
hear about the big fight they're having at
the Legion stadium in
a couple of weeks to look at offering
five hundred out of around for anybody to
stick one of them up into and. I'm going
in and buy them all I have to do it then
it might be
a four ounce four times five out of the two
thousand bucks in the bag you're crazy
. But he's a professional fighter
he's. Like anybody would because
a fighter like that it.
Wouldn't matter much. So I
want to know you're looking
for me I'll go in there and bang
the end of the biggest guy I know.
Kind of like.
What do you.
Mean you just want.
To. I guess right now back Dr Jack
Jack Hi Jack you have to decide you've
been uptight but actually I.
When did you take that was when
you was in luck and I thought I told you
the lie of that stuff when I talk about
taking my question a lot harder than
I do. Like even if you double booked
a little bit let me work got a donut I'm
a tweet Boston I. Like
to look at the way got his
right hand stuck out so
a guy gets up out of his grave sticks out
his right hand just so you can make the
bench and prove that all the rest of the
Around here a dope I tell you I got
a hunch that's Johnny Bradfield
they don't take the maybe
a month to find out but it's what drives
well that two months type two years right
is a picture postcard Agawam
Laughs Well you will have to have
a lot of you too are funny or maybe
I would maybe are after later.
These gloves used by get me one in shallow
shape. But does look eleven when you get
a project we had seven dollars
and sixty cents more. You know.
But it's actually. Rated more to wait
a minute I got an idea
come up. With the new.
Life. Douglas Williams.
Name Morency Spitz Jr to give.
Me the Money don't we just
stop. We should be officers doesn't make
a return from the telegraph pole it
is breaking my heart. That you are so
lazy adults don't you read any books you
think you're smart they call us the
geniuses. What kind of camera is that it's
a motion picture camera. Let me
say that I was guided by the guy.
To say look we got to get it
honestly see exactly like.
God I had
a good Douglas. I got to get I want to.
Play. The game we're going to play
poker. You know to play poker
No we could teach you how it's very easy
we've got no time to learn to get it so
young anyway the to I'm twelve and I
could learn that he was told what he is
a gang should we let him in God I got the
right back with the weight I've only got
twenty five right now it's OK good you don't
need not go to places. Like you'd like
to get the number of hydrogen is what it
was like what's going on behind the actual
all. Right.
So. He will try Joyce. A dip
before cards but Douglas Jr.
Said. Well it's between you
want Angel now but he got
Angel I got for seven Old Men are all the
same suit Yeah yeah yeah but there ain't
a peer in upon angels there are seven when
all I see now you've got to have pair.
You'll catch on this Yes Douglas Don't you
know you can take off the Cotton Belt Oh
you mean I do that you don't win well maybe
you want to back my fan. Just put it
over there I don't. Get to come back on
the little hand later. I am I already got
all the bad times I have it was somewhat
lacking I will tell you all right
when it's. All done you know wish
thing I'm past that so I. Can
trick. I got well but he got me on just
a measly two I don't tie no you've
got to if you want to go on
a nice little bit. Of the stay up there
I would already know that didn't take
long did it done. A lot
of hype and the you know
just the part of the guy with the whip it
out of my crotch rocket hot all over the
place like the plot I'm looking for.
Wolf. I write. The set of
the head of said OK I had
this going to want to be quick and he said
something like get married but going to
get a whack at that guy I felt
that way about. My what I've got
a lot of money and they went. What are
you fighting for. I'm going to have
a kid. Affection and. Good luck.
On the good business and I wanted to have
a few laughs I wanted you want
because I was I can get on
a rink aren't I this guy JACK DORSEY Yes
out for such Me Mr That'll be three
thirty OK Michael.
Holmes. The it makes you
think we need to McQueen We don't even
want Craig if they You're right Dan if you
want I want to have a black eye and
a big rig like following the date you
know what the sex was the fact that the
minute they think that. I apologize I just
think he paid how do you know why people
just told me just go by his truck and he
said that the doctor said that attack was
unhealthy couldn't live out
of the car that I have.
A high floor like I. Have it.
Was
a chance to have the gang of myself and
family Peggy Lee take this occasion on the
eve of the big fight but then she
would this little token of our stink.
Look at. Sorry. I can't
fight. The Dr sent me down and I'm the
matter with my ticket.
Why.
Come on.
What's the matter with everybody they
know you're lying to make you pass that
medical exam is this and Peggy I talked
to the doctor at the right here and told
what the doctor. I saw. Them yes.
Enough that. I'm
a liar and I. Lost my nerve
to go at that. Jack when
you tell me when you were you lying to me
when you told me that you're looking. For
what's that got to do with it every. Because
when you love someone you don't lie to
you don't hold anything back what
are you talking about what back.
Then. I love you too and I know your
mother clearly there's something else.
That's right a mouth to mouth
turned up by and about
a Sponge Bob and I was going to
go. With my idea about the fight
but I changed my mind saying the guy's
too big too tough I'm no sucka say why
should I get my head knocked off when I
get those some other way that's all there
is to it. Me alone can't you.
When you leave me alone.
With.
That the Holy Ghost of like that's all
it was like yeah to get that way none of
that got what it takes so much the whole
must like that guy shut up. Jack in a fit
a nobody state or not Jack and afraid not
much you yanks got. The ticket alone Sure
it's a great look like
a yellow dog slug blame
it on the ticket. Jack
.
Going away Jack. And. If you are what.
I said I'd go with just a ghost to get
a jet nobody go to maybe. I
just like maybe I don't need
over. I. I travel alone.
You. Can sure change. It so make no
difference to me with the kids
and women I know you can find in
a guy I am afraid of you if anybody I know
that shut up stop talking about excited
Jack. But I want to stay with it if you
made up your mind yeah I mean I'm on my you
must have your ease sure I got
my worries. To Kate. If you
think. What I'm trying to tell you.
I'm with you if you want to take me.
And lose weight. Eat go it's
a must stay right here if you can to fight
what do you think it would be if it was
as if I knew it was all a
time when I tell a guy and
a while you tell him
tell him all. The way.
And you say five and.
Post
a pic didn't see no
south. He wouldn't be so
sure was Johnny Bradfield.
The the.
Spirit of Cricket got to take. What
it takes to protect six because.
There's only two here where is the other
but is this then there's only to let me
want to what you want to let.
Him I Said he thought. Like
a bad. Guy and I bought the
album. Title from. My album. I think.
What the deal is that your exact go take
a white guy. But that wasn't. Coming so I.
Think. We all know that.
He's
a God I'm going to. Shake and
jump on it as I write. I
wait a minute we during
a town. I'm always what
somebody else can't.
I'm not afraid of anybody I know I take it
easy well yeah yeah exactly and he just
a big baby that's. You.
And insist it's very. Pretty just
Mary and me I know that rocket fire
and fire I want to come testify in your
fictional paper and I couldn't wait to get
below zero you know go OK I mean.
I'm getting out of here like
crazy. And I have such
a piece of one rock
that's reducing. Already
so I'll just give the can just my way to
China trying to get my goat soften it up
and make it one which we're
going to need to up.
My game a way so she has
a site here thanks so much really. What
are we left with not
a word about the wife you know and I get
that hospital bill paid about what I said
I want to buck up but. I have
to. Sign up pretty soon.
Well enough Right right right.
I'm going to Mars.
Must be Coloccini. And I don't. Think
that's funny just because it is
real way from my son I should take the
first one I'm coming to you and. Their
fear going away that's what
I'm going. To take first.
This is the way oh fuck that up just to see
that's what he gets the company Yeah I
know OK OK let's go get it was meant for
me trying to get my goat out that's good
you have no idea I want to go on had been
OK with that the others on the right my.
God I saw a story I had time to check
a. Box today here's where it
says Come on. Good luck to.
You. My life. Is down because this
is down right. It's rather. Than that and.
That. I had
a ball and Jack darn it.
Showed that because we had
a lot enough RAM is also
a tough one I just kept trying
to but that's. Just. I think.
I take it. Oh Jackson's not
T.V.'s back fight for.
It and I'm sure I got our baby
over today all right yes. Yes I'm
a. Pain guy.
And as I got out I got it
yes. Oh I don't I. Know I'm.
Not
a Cinnabon my life. I
am the challenge for the ME the wild won't
just don't say that out there and I.
Found the right think not if we burrow Oh
boy was holding him and his knowledge was
right it was.
There
that I met him and I do it. Right
there at the Pentagon
if I thank you that's
a print of my journey back and I'll
be up again for Jagger remark is is.
There.
A way to get back in effect
if you know. That my
there.
There that get it you
know that you know yes.
I think it's funny how to find a
balance right after the death of
a test event or is sent back.
To Earth and then for the
credit card you saw one for the left the
job and another heart by pass. Out.
To me by. Him I just can't
overwrite what is it you are.
Saying get out and just. Read.
There. That much I
think.
And you get
a good thanks it's been this funny
I'm going to fight you way but it's
a crime and I'm not an addict. There
right. There.
Right.
Age. Now.
They're just about again that don't
have actual contact that's like
that's done overseas for the fun of it
out there and thank God that is not from
a critic like that of God to. Me
and I his family were all day she
explained that. I would. Not
follow along.
Yes.
I think there's
a cell phone as you would like I don't.
Need to manage you know. The only question
asked it's a hundred bucks the I think
that's a good OK well about Saved I'm
a bell save it take I'm going to post
a little bit now about how do you like it
because one more magical place we have
let me ask. You. Now.
Well it's all right.
Now are you.
Going to let that big look I look I am
a Johnny gone we don't want to go to
bed right tonight and I don't know.
Now. Yet.
They're all right Aaron.
Why did I tell ye I. Say
that again pipe down.
Putting. My jacket didn't
want transferred to yourself I got out of
the second place you got to go you can
quit I guess that's what you look I think
we don't need we would still need to go
on Spence we got you was.
Eight years it's hard to take
a word for this. You.
Know.
They're
all right there. You
know get up raised it.
This. Way.
Well it's
a pretty bad beating but you come out
of it all right. Back where you were on
how he talked just about to say oh Jack get
up did you get up did you try going to
get We've done all we can for well you
know I'm going to do much for that little
kid me
a trumpet cello just come out of Jesse
Jackson come out of the gym. Oh he did it
down for us he went talking talking just
to just put us on jacket and it's on right
you we got the money. And oh Johnny
jacks the name. He is just
a sentiment. You fought the good fight
you know if it's good enough is it
out of my body you know like the guy
got it it was the dog so I just got
a better idea of what it brought it
that I feel by what I tell you just
a little would do that too I'll give him
another chance to really take on what Jay
The idea what I have I
gotta go now go I mean
I got I got to get dressed I don't
have I come on get out of the I'm
a rap but the guy like oh oh. Oh we got.
Your I call it Chris I'll
be right with you haven't.
Checked your I can't
find time with way just
a second time and I gotta tell pinky
something. It's not money I want to copy it.
No kidding it took
a couple of fights for me back to his
manager actually was too literally. Eliahu
you actually know. He's blind
to me and. Tell me the truth
no I'm not he's my manager. Sure his
manager is he going to take me back to the
governor Bob lined up me I'm going to pick
up leaving cash and I'm going to Mike
that is honest and about ten years is just
clowning that's all that money ever does
anything for gags every day the engines are
real good to see him soon and you know
you want to go to bonds Damita you know
when I stand to think like that one of us
and they are coming right back to you I'm
going with none I can yes you can because
because this is
a state. We're going to
stick we fail Yeah woman
is the project what is it tell me please
there's nothing wrong with my package and
where I can. Get it and it is
a group going to have. A good weekend you
gotta stick with grandma and the kids
come on. We gotta get going.
To shake. It if you're just kiss me what's
meant go quickly. Because if you don't
I'm going to get optimistic.
Going to. Thank you.
Enough Ellen Goodman are expected to be
a stylist I'm not complaining I know I
today I'm not sure I should. When you get
back to town
a male follow you right down Broadway with
confetti and everything you'll probably
be
a big shot headquarters from our set it think
it we're going to cover the government
for
a day I depend on your award I
will give you any trouble OK. Jack
. Go on home going away I got
a kid we don't need you're on here talking
to you know. I tried to go home yet
would you take me with you I put
it on home found I got a deal on
a kind of privacy I'd like to take it with
me but I can't it's big to you and it's
SO THAT'S RIGHT not going
away it's. Gotta go back
and get that gas station got
it you know it was you.
Thank you gonna sing for the works. It's
a good tip. Makes no
difference to may say I'm
a cop doing the job I know what I like
and I'm not saying you don't. Get
one tip. But he was like
with the right. Yeah.
It's job a good lawyer my present
up. Being a tough one. If I get
a good lawyer will know that
it's in your business mind.
Is no. Let's go. It's well looking De
Molay behind and I feel kind of hard oh
I don't like my God send up the guy the
bird he had a wife that day and said
goodbye to use you know just like
a mouse hold to the sit up like.
That old lady. Is sure to
go the white haired boy doesn't look bad
I'm going back and take whatever is coming
I'm a bit slow to step in and put
a thing on I WAS JUST THINKING IT'S MY
GOD I give you head and I just said why
don't the damn them kids
are never found. It was
a terrible saga come and then.
I do it again. Now if Paisley
automates. I made one mistake in my.
Day Maybe I'm making it up maybe
I got the wrong guy maybe
a yeah maybe I have Wise Guys I'm
not quite sure all. Gone case.
That's it I'm going out of a cab I had
a paragraph. Talk don't. Talk
on.
What if you think you
have gone guilt. About.
The
elite.
Elite
.